sup everyone chambers wanted people fast
he was a very special video today now
before I say anything this something I
gotta say and I can't stress it enough
when I said this story that I'm not to
tell you [ __ ] is something that I
debated over and over and over again if
I was even going to put it on my EQ page
because the stewards I sell it's it is
very dark it's horrible it's twisted to
be honest it does even have a happy
ending but I thought about it more and
more and I realize I gotta tell the
story if only if only to protect you not
because it's something people who watch
talk Underground need to know because if
they don't they're in trouble [ __ ]
so everybody sit back relax pull the
seat up and make sure to keep the lights
on because we're about to go over the
story of the red Manic
now before I go on explain what exactly
the red Mac is I gotta explain something
first a lot of people actually believe
in the urban legend that if you so much
as look at the picture of the red Matic
you will be cursed for all eternity now
I personally don't know how true this is
however do have been officially reported
deaths of by people who have died and
the families and friends have blamed
their deaths on the red Manic so that
alone should you idea on how legit this
[ __ ] is if you want to see what he
looks like
I'll put a picture now however if you
don't I don't blame you so look away in
three two
okay you can look back [ __ ] as you
saw it looks just like Max official
concept out for soccer but he is
arriving Center brain crazy hump [ __ ]
now that you know who the [ __ ] Mack is
what do you say we dive into history and
see just who the [ __ ] he killed and how
many life is ruined
it was the late nineties the TV show
soccer had just begun production and
nobody in that room had any idea that
sock on the ground we're gonna be as big
as it was an especially mad the
Hedgehog's popularity and [ __ ] now the
picture you're looking at is an actual
picture for like 1996 or some [ __ ] of a
bunch of people on the computers working
together to come up with the design for
the character of the show it's widely
believed which here to keep us but it's
believed that first was Sonya I first
was Sonic cuz you know he saw a Jack and
[ __ ]
then with Sonya but for it but for some
God knows reason nobody could come up
with the design of Magna Hedgehog until
Wonga his name was Gregory boron like as
a lot of people may know he is now
famous as the sock under an Al director
but then he wasn't famous [ __ ] he was
some random janitor who was like working
in the oxen [ __ ] and late one night he
just drew magnet on a piece of paper and
then when I his boss and she came in the
next day he felt so damn that's so good
what colors are you gonna be and Gregory
thought wanna make him green it would go
good with blue and blue and pink and
[ __ ] and he thought yeah we'll do that
however that didn't exactly go as
planned the very next day Bishop Gregory
Thunder coma he he was on the brink of
life and death like however he did a
Vinci wake up like a week later after
falling in his coma saying that the
relief in juris coma was that he was
humanik with green pegs like his boss's
head home - and [ __ ]
however he acts he knocked over a can of
red paint which fell on the picture and
he said when it hit the picture it's as
if it wasn't paid anymore any turn like
blood into blood like people thought he
was crazy and said Gregory you're just
imagining but he said no I know what I
sighed after that he would fall straight
back his coma however this time it would
be off and on with him waking up every
other day and [ __ ] he would say really
creepy things like no stay away from me
red Manic is at the foot of the bed he's
gonna get my get away [ __ ] I'll be your
[ __ ] ass why you red I made you green
you were supposed to be green and he
would not do that non-stop for like
hours or even days on end like a little
[ __ ] like talking to an invisible Manic
that wasn't even there and [ __ ] at least
to us he wasn't there but to him he said
he was now while Gregory Bowen was in
the hospital ship back at the office
what him and his coworker booked some
eerie [ __ ] was going down and [ __ ] like
some co-workers the next day they would
complain that there will be a chill in
the air or something was grabbing their
ass and [ __ ] like nuts like and he
thought it was a ghost like as a matter
of fact [ __ ] the pictures that you
look at now was actually a picture that
was taken by one security cameras if you
look on the far left you can see what
some people believe is actually the red
man egg like over that guy's shoulder
and [ __ ] if you can't see it all circle
it now to make it easier for you to see
now I don't know about you [ __ ] but
that sends chills Rob up my [ __ ] ass
like if I saw that in security camera I
would think yup red Mac is real like
[ __ ] it [ __ ] him in the ass and we'll
attack about things let's get out and as
a matter fact allow people who work
there actually did because because they
would suck they get to the point where
they would see red Manic like not just
insecure accounts but standing across
the hallway just like staring at them
and [ __ ] or like whole drum sticks like
he's throwing you shove the jump zips up
your ass I mean that's [ __ ] creepy
like like iuk me [ __ ] know what [ __ ]
[ __ ] you man but no but that's not all
it got to the point you're people
claiming that you're like following them
home and [ __ ] in fact here is another
photo that somebody took and claimed
that mal could find them if you look in
back you can actually see red Max
standing in the distance as if he's not
going to rape that matter some [ __ ] and
if you look at the man's face it looks
like he's running 4th [ __ ] laugh
like he really wants to get away from
the red migi and [ __ ] but man cool name
go here is another picture that was
actually taken by one of our directors
while walking talked on the ground [ __ ]
while he was driving away he looked
behind him and apparently saw like what
appeared to be like red Manic like
driving a car and [ __ ] like like look at
that right there
so go back to just he can see and [ __ ]
like who would've thought that red Manic
knew how to drive like an automotive
vehicle or some [ __ ] but apparently
apparently red Mack and
Jack-of-all-trades like like you can get
away from him while all this was going
on Greggy Bourne was still in the
hospital and sadly as many of you may
already know he didn't make it he would
die in his Sleet dreaming about like
Maddox
I'm sharing how he wishes us never happy
- am I I don't give a [ __ ]
although before he did he did say a
couple of things that will chill your
smelly ass to the core lock like I'm not
even kidding you you can actually go to
this website it
do you like look at like a bit early
reports of like people who are God and
it'll tell you to like final woods and
[ __ ] and all actually read down what it
says his father woods before you read
Manic is right there he's gonna get my
ass he's gonna kill me what he just paid
my did y'all see that [ __ ] he faked math
why you faking my ass [ __ ] you want to
go you're [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] why you
speaking miles I'll beat your ass
help help help
he's trying to rape my oh you'll see
this [ __ ] he tried to rape my [ __ ]
ass I'll rape your ass [ __ ] you wanna
go come on come on
I'll rape your [ __ ] ass I won't hold
back [ __ ] I'll rape your [ __ ] red
ass you were supposed to be great [ __ ]
[ __ ] and those were his final words
before his life was to supposedly taken
by the red Manor so remember everyone
you don't always know it's out there in
the middle of the night red Manic might
be coming for you next